welcome back this is the last Talk of
the afternoon in this theater after this
talk is finished at 4:00 we'll have the
lightning talks in the big theater
theater 5 they should be quite
exciting and now I'd like to turn it
over to Mohit Sedana and Tom bergman's
to tell you
well H testing vectors I think I can
figure that
out yeah so good afternoon everyone um
here I'm U my name is m Sana working as
a search architect for WTO Clover where
uh together with my colleague Tom bman
um we're working in a search team um
focusing on uh development of a very
matur keyword search
such uh
functionality and uh we like to ask
maybe Tom also to introduce himself yeah
my name is Tom bman uh technology
product owner and team lead of thearch
Team yeah so a bit more about wter CL so
if you're not familiar volto Clover is a
company where uh we provide access to
the information to the Professionals in
different domains like tax legal
Healthcare uh compliance uh by offering
many online Solutions and in these
Solutions uh we offer access to millions
of documents where our users can uh
perform full Tech search uh doing their
research and finding the information
they need to fulfill the uh needs of
their end
users so bit of introduction what we
would like to talk about today is our
journey uh where we would like to
discuss our um learn ings uh by uh
applying series of experiments where we
IND where we conducted uh tests uh to to
to test the the capabilities of vector
search uh while uh maintaining our
keyword search functionalities as it is
uh as we all know Vector search is um
The Game Changer uh because it's uh in
the field of information
retrieval uh it not only allows for
searching for keywords but actual
meaning um unlocking different use cases
so we see more and more uh uh how uh
users are searching for the information
and and how they're consuming that
information is Ever Changing looking at
this very beautiful picture is actually
uh very famous way of uh summarizing the
it's called Gartner hyp cycle which is a
graph where uh which summarizes the the
five stages of um of a of a new
innovation from The Innovation to the
hype and then it looks like it's a
silver bullet which will solve all the
problems but as we know uh
um uh you go through a phase of
disappointment where it doesn't deliver
and then from there uh the understanding
at widespread adoption of that uh uh so
why is large scale testing is very
crucial uh because uh firstly in real
world applications we are mass we are
dealing with massive data sites so we
have millions of documents which should
be converted to vectors but also uh at
the same time finding a balance between
the quality so we saw an earlier talk
where we talked about Vector surge is a
really cool but uh when you talk about
surge you also expect other features to
be part of it like spell spell checking
facets
filtering um but at the same time also
Main maintaining a balance uh uh because
it can really blow up your cost because
Vector search is expensive in terms of
uh uh time and the money you spend on
it so we divided this task into actually
two parts the first talk first part is
given a piece of text uh give you have a
model which you can use to convert those
text uh to to compute them embeddings
and from our initial research when we
started with these experiments this is
one of the things which came up a lot
that uh in doing Computing embeddings
and inference is the pain Point uh
because it's it just doesn't scale uh
but also uh doing the actual Ann search
which I think uh which my colleague Tom
is going to talk more about in
detail so we're going to f I'm going to
focus on uh this part Computing em
embeddings so what we did we started
with the experiments uh
our experiments where we took variable
length of text thousand queries
different lens but also four open source
models uh with different dimensions uh
call it small medium large uh and we
developed uh inferencing service where
uh you give it a piece of a text and
then it computes the vectors and while
we did that we actually tested this with
100 threads so that was our
Baseline uh a big a small disclaimer
uh we are part of the production team so
we are not uh machine learning Engineers
so when we started with the journey uh
we started with with very na approach
that we didn't know much about Vector
search or Computing embeddings
so uh this graph is a little bit funny
one because you don't see those uh first
rows because they were very small you
didn't have a time to fix it here uh but
this was the the first slide we want to
talk about uh when we started testing
our uh testing the query inferencing
part we wanted to know what kind of
machine do you really need to run that
influencing uh service um so we started
with uh with uh deploying our services
to the regular CPU machines but we also
soon found found out that they will not
scale up uh and uh GPU so we we also
tested those on GPU machines and uh we
also looked at these special chips which
are uh called Advanced Vector
instructions it's a special type of
instruction sets which are optimized for
only
CPU uh what we found out that uh in
order to do INF frence uh or computer
embeddings GPU was the clear winner and
uh because when we really tested this
with 100 threads uh those uh graphs as
you can see the query latencies were
really really high especially with
larger models uh and and this was one of
the learnings we so in order to do
inferencing you need really GPU
power uh the second test we did actually
is what is the correlation between the
text length and the embedding inference
latency itself
um so if you look at the graphs you can
see the very tiny uh paks where we
tested it also with four models so uh
Computing uh embeddings with different
dimensions
and what we also found here is that uh
those larger models where we Computing
thousands of embeddings this
case24 uh putting a load on the system
and uh with more uh number of tokens uh
they really uh uh the the Laten has grow
very exp exponentially sorry uh so this
is because those larger models are uh
Computing vectors for each of the tokens
and then this was one of the very nice
learning because you have to do this not
only at query time but also at index
time so you have to conjunct your text
into into uh sections and then use that
for for computing the
embeddings this is a slide it is a
common knowledge but we included it here
so how this will perform if we put a lot
of lot of load on the system so we
tested with 100 uh
but we also tested our services uh the
inferencing part uh with uh more and
more uh uh uh concurrent uh users so all
the way to 800 and this what what this
uh what we learned here is that the the
the high number of thread uh how much it
impacts the the the embedding
calculations especially with those large
models
so going to the next slide and
while we were doing this research we
also learned uh along the way uh use
onnx so onnx stands for opal neural
network exchange it's a format which you
can convert your models and this was a
great performance booster U especially
on uh we used the special runtime for
this so on an X with GPU and this was a
clear winner that doing inferencing with
onnx and GPU the query lenses were under
50 milliseconds for uh those 100 uh
threads we are not done yet uh so we're
still exploring this uh very exciting
domain uh and there are some uh other
things we are currently working on for
example converting models to onx was
really a game changer for us but also
applying more optimizations to the model
so applying like constant folding or uh
quantization so from our earlier test uh
using those floats uh and can be very
heavy on performance so from there if
you go to int uh uh it it was really uh
uh uh like 50% better than uh what we
saw with with with our first test but
also scaling out the embedding service
so we tested it with 800 threads but
with only one server but can we also
just test this uh by scaling
horizontally or vertically and uh use
that knowledge to to improve to
implement a solution which will which
can be deployed to
production so once we had the embeddings
uh we could just go and use our choice
of search engine we have uh been using
solar for uh for a number of years and
Tom is going to talk about uh how we
tested Ann
search
yes all right I'm going to show even
more numbers and more graphs and I
realized it's the latest uh the last uh
full Talk of the day so I try to do my
best to keep it very
interesting right so yeah we have this
two sides of factor search one was the
inflence side we talked about and now
I'm going to talk about Ann search so
that's what happened after we got the
vector from the inference site so um
yeah Vector search is a different thing
than uh than than keyword search than
searching an inverted index inverted
index is table look up words and then
find documents that belong to each word
but Vector search is traversing a graph
and that works very differently than
than the laws of physics works just
differently for Vector search it's
literally hoping from one node to
another node to find the spot in that
graph that is most closest to the vector
of the query and that's uh yeah we will
we just want to try to find out what are
the parameters what makes this fast and
what makes it slow right we try to to
learn everything about it so let's go to
that Journey uh first this is our uh
situation our defaults in the test that
we want to conduct um index 2.6 million
documents um index is in an fairly large
machine of 128 gab of memory so to just
to make sure that the whole index fits
in it um also use 100 concurrent users
uh to pound the system with ques uh in
between the calls there's one uh second
of pause so uh it means that we have 100
QPS at maximum which is kind of close to
the um um to a busy day on one of our
major products right so it's we choose
that
deliberately uh also interesting to say
we made sure that every query that a
threat executes is a unique uh Factor uh
just to make sure that we are not
testing the cach but we are testing real
performance of the calculation and I use
four different models for that and uh
for the rest we I can say we just took
the solar defaults that are there as a
default right but we we going to vary
with each of these uh uh parameters that
too so the first Lessons Learned and
it's a very important one is that to
realize that um a Lucine index is built
of
segments and uh segments are there for
good reason so segments uh are there in
the Sol index to make sure that whenever
you got new content or updates um you're
gotten quickly available and at the same
time a segment is immutable so it makes
sure that the index is very stable and
doesn't get
corrupt but there appears to be a
problem for Factor search um each of
those segments are their own hnsw graph
and I have the strong impression that if
you do this in Solo the current search
it searches them uh in sequence which uh
means that it takes a lot of time before
we got results right I was kind of
underwhelmed with the test results uh
when I was doing those tests and I I
went to the slack Channel relevance
check SL Channel start talking about it
and somebody suggested to me did you
ever thought about merging your segments
I never thought about it it was never a
concern in keyword search world we just
went with the solar
defaults um but anyway I did it I just
uh did a force optimize got one segment
it took a lot of time because but it
made a whole lot of difference and even
to uh to an amount that my search
latencies got down but U yeah 10 times
quicker search results so I had to throw
away all my test results so far and
start over again and that was the bad
news the good news is at least I got
something uh which is way quicker
knowing that a forced optimize is not
something that you would ideally want to
have in in production system where you
got constant updates so um yeah it it
requires to think about a a merging
strategy uh again uh which maybe you
took for granted on an keyword search
situation but since it's now Vector
search and it appears to very s to be
very sensitive to
segments uh
merging has to happen in some way so
that's what the title uh basically says
uh cat your segments together
right so um with that lesson learned uh
for the rest of the test I did it all
with fully optimized index
so okay if we index a piece of content
right a set of content how does that uh
um have an impact on the size of the
index and this is what the first graph
will show you uh those 2.6 million
documents indexed without any
vectorization uh is about 7 gabt pick
but the moment we start to vectorize the
abstract which we I we index metline
content which contains metadata and
Abstract we indexed uh we factorized the
abstract with different models and you
can really see the impact of just doing
that how big that uh that index grows so
a vector is a large piece of metadata
that you have to index and uh it could
even double the index size and also the
index speed uh will go up if you uh
factorize
content so that's expected I think but
now we know how much it will differ
especially for that content
set on the query side
um actually were pretty good results so
these are latency numbers and we see
milliseconds there and uh for a Content
set of several million documents we got
very low latencies with the default um
um parameters that we uh took for our uh
stress test uh there are a couple of
spikes there with the 10 million
documents but that is not because of the
10 million I guess but it is because of
those tests were done when there were
three segments instead of one
so but this amount of volume with these
parameters test results are pretty okay
uh but we are not done yet so um knowing
that we could handle that amount of
content um I created couple of
collections with uh
varying um content sets and start just
uh querying multiple collections at the
same time just to see how that behaves
and uh you can see below the uh amount
yeah the combined size of all those
collections that were cre simultaneously
with the amount of users of threats and
um still very good results even the on
the very right we see there are 50
million documents quered at the same
time with 300 users um very good results
with one exception there there's this
one big spike this was an combination of
um collections that together took more
than 128 of gigabyt big in in content
size or in index size so and then
suddenly we got the the data SE go
through the roof so there is a big
lesson learned here make really sure
that if you have a vector index that it
all fits into memory because the moment
it doesn't then you get this enormous
spike in latencies
there going on to the K value so K value
is something that you have to specify at
query time which indicates how many
results you would like to get back from
a factor
um important to know is that K value is
not just the number K value is also a
relevancy driver because the higher you
make K the more likely it will be that
the uh best documents appear in the top
10 of your search results or the top X
so it makes sense to increase Decay
value just to make sure that your very
top Factor search results are of better
quality and in that sense it um yeah it
is just interesting to know how far can
we stretch K until we got into uh
problems right and of course the
expectation is the higher K we make the
more work it has to do so probably
latest SE will go up and that's indeed
what we saw here so here we see the test
results for each
model um you see the test results there
with increasing values of K uh so for
all models it goes pretty fine uh up to
K of thousand but the moment you got
multiple thousands then yeah you cut
into the problem spaces there
of course it depends on your use case if
it's acceptable or
not going on to similarity function
there's also something you can vary with
so our uh search engine that we tested
supports three different kind of
calculations to measure uh factors with
each other ukian cine and do product um
UC is the distance between vectors coine
measures the angle between vectors and
Ault product is mix of both and if you
look at the uh just the calculation the
the the actual formula for calculating
each of these similarities then you
would expect just based on the
complexity of a calculation that the
product is the easy one it's the most
performing one just because it's the
most simple calculation that you have to
make and um that cine would be the least
performing one so that's expectation and
these are test results and indeed so
here you can see each color each
function gets its own color and indeed
the product appears to be the most
performing way of calculating factors
with each other that's expected now the
interesting part here that coine is
indeed the least performing one but only
for low K
values right the moment that we got to
high K values like around 3,000 10 you
suddenly see that ukian gets more
expensive and why is that I have no real
real no idea so if somebody knows please
let me
know uh I have no idea why K value would
be of any impact on the calculation of a
factor and why that would be different
but that was probably good explanation
because uh it looks like there's a very
uh let's say consistent pattern that we
see yeah it's not just
a yeah
coincidence all right factor and coding
so by default a vector is a bunch of
floats that's the the default way of uh
representing a vector but Lucine
supports two ways of uh encoding a
vector as a float which uh occupies four
bytes or as a bite which occupies one
b and uh we just like to know okay one
or the other what does the what does the
impact have on on uh the content size uh
the index size and also the the qu
latency um by the way you can change a
float factor into a bite factor and if
you do that it's called scalar
quantization um you have to be careful
about how you're going to use that bite
Factor so uh it depends on the
similarity function that you're going to
use what the correct way is of
quantizing that factor um do you want to
maintain the angle in case you would
like to use coine similarity or do you
want to contain the relative distance
and in that way another way of
quantization uh needs to happen so that
that is a side note we took the angle
approach because it's uh a simpler one
um but yeah I mean that's something to
to to keep in mind once you start doing
that so the expectation is that if we
change a float value a float Vector into
a bite Vector do that both on query side
and on the content side that at least
index size would go down but also it may
probably have an positive effect on the
latencies because it's it may be much
easier to calculate with a simpler
Vector representation like that
so first the index size and indeed yes
index size goes down not like four times
down which you may want to expect if you
change something from four byes to one
bite but at least for the larger vectors
we see uh well uh half of the index size
that we had before right we have float
on left and bite and
right the index speed um not so much
difference over
there uh the query
side also
there uh it makes indeed sense to um
quantize your factors into uh the bite
variant uh because there are latencies
goes down as well of course if you do
this it comes with procision loss so
it's it's not just we training here
relevancy against speed but that's
that's like always the moment you make
decisions um we have to balance
somewhere in this triangle of speed
versus cost versus uh relevance
okay I'm going to a talk about a stress
test so um this is about okay let's just
increase the amount of threats the
amount of users and then see where the
system starts to crack so how many
concurrent users can we uh let uh the
system
handle um also here there's a
distinction between a float and a bite
because we already thought well if you
put uh index vectors as bytes it will
probably be able to handle more stress
than if it would be just floats and that
is indeed exactly what we see here so
and also these small models can handle
larger loads than the big models so on
the Y the the X AIS we see here the
amount of users that we concurrently let
the system um
handle and yeah this is pretty good
because um at least for us the stress
that we usually see on the system is
about like 4 400 users at the same time
making queries each second and and here
we can see it already goes to the
thousands and we still got pretty good
results so that's an encouraging uh uh
graph at
least so I'm going on to filtering and
this is really where you can see how
Vector search is different compared to
uh inverted index search um
filtering uh means that the moment that
you are actually say well a subset of
our content is not accessible it means
that in this graph the hnsw graph you
create noes that are that end roads so
you make the graph less reversible by
applying a
filter and it means that the expectation
is that the moment you add a filter to a
vector search query that latencies would
go up and that's exactly the opposite of
what you have with inverted index you
apply a filter there then usually that's
gets a faster result now how much does a
filter impact Vector search and that's
what we wanted to test and we have some
very interesting uh observations there
and here you can see indeed the moment
that we add filters especially if you
start to narrow the scope more down so
from left to right we got a more narrow
scope you see latencies go up and um for
the small models it kind of stays within
acceptable ranges there uh but the
moment we have some models there
especially the one on the very right you
see it it got some very Pro problematic
uh search results and suddenly so use
them we got a problem um if you make the
scope very narrow then later seat go up
again well go down I mean so we got good
performance there and this is because
there is a feature in Lucine that uh
switches from Graph Search to brute
force uh K&N search the moment that the
filter is so narrow that it passes some
kind of a threshold so we see clearly
that feature here on action but there is
this bandwidth some some problem area
there in the Middle where you can see
well that is kind of between one and 5%
of the search results in our case at
least we see there are very high
latencies so need to find a fix for
that and by the way if you look closely
to that yellow area there uh we got two
filter situations that got uh basically
the same amount of results back but one
filter performs poorly and the other one
does Rel ly okay what's going on
there first that was a real head
scratcher I had no idea but uh then I
started to see one particular thing is
that the problem filter on the on the
left here had only one term in the query
while the Performing one had multiple
terms in the query so uh it's it's not a
coincidence I got multiple cases where
the one- term filter performed way
poorer than the the multi-term
filter I I have also no idea why is that
the case but I have a theory at least is
that the one term filter um those term
those documents that passes the filter
appear close to each other in that graph
in the hmw graph and therefore the blind
spot around it is also bigger well on
the right side you see the the results
are more distributed across the graph
and probably in that situation this
graph is better traversible than this
graph although there the same amount of
documents that are actually allowed to
pass the
filter how true is this I have no idea
but this sounds plausible to me and
there's so far nobody yet that that said
the opposite so I asked this question in
the slack Channel
too um but yeah so we had still that
problem that for some filters uh you
know this one to filter is something
that can happen user can just select it
so we need to find a way in order to
bring down the latery for that filter
and maybe the next thing that we're
going to try is a possible solution so
this is the hnsw max connections uh
parameter uh also called M Max or M
sometimes and what this specify is the
amount of connections that each node can
have to uh other nodes in in the graph
and the idea is that well if I increase
the amount of connections there then
probably that makes the graph better
traversible um especially if you apply
filter
them also it comes with the cost it
takes longer to index and I thought if
we would do that it would probably also
increase the index size now about that
last one we got a very interesting
result that it appears to be that's
totally not the case right so I in I
increase the amount of uh of of
connections but for some reason it does
not impact at all the index
size so what's going on there again I
have no idea right I've got a lot of
questions all of in the this test
result could it be that this parameter
is not working at all or could it be
that maybe in solar or luine there's
there a fixed amount of bytes reserved
for the amount of connections and
therefore we don't see the uh we see we
don't see it
here again if somebody knows please tell
me so uh yeah the index speed I mean we
see a bit of an uptick there not so much
but uh did it work on the query side so
did it really solve our uh filter
problem and um it looks like maybe the
answer is yes but it's a maybe here you
know on the right side you see some
problem filters there which had very
high latencies and then I started to
increase the uh the M Factor right the
uh from 16 which is a default to 32 to
46 uh
64 and yes if I up uh if I create higher
values then latencies go down but they
don't go down with higher increases of
the M value so I'm not really sure if
that actually was the fix right it could
be that maybe um every time we built up
a new index um uh there's always
Randomness involved and we recreated the
index a lot of times and that Randomness
is maybe the reason why the first try we
got as very high latencies and later we
didn't get them maybe it was the M
Factor right so I I cannot and also on
the other for the other models I really
couldn't see that it actually did
increase the the latencies there so not
always at
least so this is a bit of a question
mark uh probably requires more testing
to get more uh yeah concrete answers
there the other uh query side not sorry
the other index side parameter is hns
beam withd also called EF construction
with other search engines and this is
the candidate list that is uh that the
engine keeps whenever it inserts new
documents inside the graph and the
candidate list basically is a list of
candidates where potentially this new
document could make connections too so
the reason for increasing this size is
that it has a better uh chance in order
to connect to the correct documents and
the smaller the size is the faster
indexing will happen that's the
expectation at least though the less of
the Lesser quality you would get in the
construction of that graph so in other
words it does not really do anything
with c latency is expected but it may
have some impact
on index speed and relevancy but the
relevancy side we didn't test not yet at
least right so indeed the index size is
not affected by an uh a changing value
the index speed however is impacted so
with an higher value of uh e EF search
or EF construction I mean um we got
higher index index times but also with
the lower value than than the default
100 and why is that I would expect that
to be lower I mean if you have a shorter
list it would makes uh faster to index
new documents which is not the
observation that we had so again a
question mark and no answer I'm
sorry so on the query side uh no impact
these are all very low latencies and
this variation doesn't mean anything
with those low numbers
so yeah so that's um in summary what we
did in terms of uh testing a and search
and the next slide is a bit of a
dangerous one it's a wish list and if
you put a wish list in front of an open
source Community um you got you got
reactions back like um you know index a
pull request and then we talk but with
uh the risk of getting all kind of
reactions like that um I'm doing it
anyway so a wish list that we have is
well wouldn't it be nice if there would
be no segment index for at least the h
and a w graph because we can see at
least the poor performance or maybe
there's another way um uh we saw that
there are some some um latest
developments uh in the scene and elastic
search I've seen it as well where those
seconds are being searched in parallel
rather than in sequence which can also
already be a big help and maybe that I
hope at least that in Solo we also get
this kind of development soon so the
other thing is to um uh have the
embeding infuencing internal so we did
it uh on the site learned some lessons
from there but uh wouldn't it be nice if
this was somehow part of the engine
itself so you don't have to take care of
that of that
externally uh internal Vector
quantization we did a very Brute Force
simple way of quantizing our vectors and
also maintaining the angle the moment
you want to maintain the distance it
requires a very more much more complex
way of uh Scala quantisation wouldn't it
be nice if the search engine was able to
just take care of that as some kind of a
post-processing uh
exercise a friendly way of hybrid search
report it's not part of the test and I
didn't tell tell about it but uh to have
hybrid search in solar it is possible
but requires big complex structures of
queries and uh we seen other Lucine
based search engines already making a
much more friendlier uh developer
friendly approach towards that and the
last part is uh uh multi field Factor
Fields now we have to chop up the
documents in order to create factors for
those chunks but um if we have this and
I know there have been talks about that
before uh that this is maybe something
that could be coming then you don't need
to chump up the documents you can just
have multiple factors in stored in the
same document so that's a wish L it
would be nice but one can only dream so
all right this um concludes our talk and
uh there's some time for questions thank
you very
[Applause]
much and since we have such a wealth of
them from from the zoom we'll start with
the
zoom Alexandra
fber is Onyx also better on
CPU take that one yeah I think uh from
our earlier tests I think we didn't find
that but uh we did some early tests and
we saw a significant Improvement if
you're using onx and quantize your
models so we did the int 8 uh
quantization and we found the results
were uh really uh better than what we
were getting the regular
CPU uh great talk I have an answer to
most of your questions but I will answer
them here we can talk later but I have a
question myself uh what jvm were you
using and um do you know if solar is
enabling
uh the Panama Vector module for simd
calculations for the jvm we were using
Java 11 uh I think so if you're using
Java 11 then yeah it may be on the slide
but I think it's jav
yeah Aruna
govu what is your approach to generate
the bite quantized
vector and you can punt on that if it's
complex' SE we'll do that for you
so the question was to bite quantize
Vector how did you do your bite
quantization okay um yeah that was a
Brute Force way as I said before so um
first we normalized the vector uh to a
standard value between uh zero and one
and that was just we still got a float
back then and then um the Second Step
was to turn that into map that into a
value between minus 127 and plus 27 so
it was this two-step approach it was I
think four lines of python code um not
ideal I must say so but uh 99 99% of the
the factors were still valid afterwards
that was a very tiny percentage which
was not but at least I uh did some uh
Hands-On uh yeah some sample experiments
to see if at least I was still able to
compare factors and still got the same
search results which is relatively what
we saw yeah so only using Co seen
similarity um that said I know it's not
ideal we have to if we want to do this
for real and production we have probably
have to go to more sophisticated
ways thanks for the great talk guys uh I
was really impressed with the results I
saw from on andx can you tell me about
the level of effort it took to implement
that and and how you went about
it uh in terms of effort I think we use
a lot of Open Source libraries and open
source models uh
all the models we use for this talk was
open open source available on hugging
phase and we use Optimum uh to convert
our models to uh to onx so in terms of
effort it was really uh not too much
because the optimum Library you we used
comes with a lot of uh uh support with
converting models to onx and even
applying further uh uh optimizations for
example one of the tests we did we
didn't share the we we didn't have a
slide for it to convert the model uh and
then optimize it for the ABX 512 vni
processor uh which is just like a one
line of python
code Kevin langang from an
infrastructure perspective how do you
simulate concurrent users multiple
threads multiple pods
machines um this was just a jmor setting
where you can just say how many threats
concur Strat you would like the system
to
generate so it is just like that all
right we had a separate jmor uh uh uh
engine or ec2 setup where where it just
runs and it simulates that amount of
traffic have you guys put put any resar
Research into the Tex bding INF by
hugging face I can take a
solo uh well for these experiments we
haven't looked at it yet yeah thank you
there uh as we were doing this research
we we were also learning more about more
and more about how do you really use
this models and optimize it and then
every day you go to a LinkedIn post
there like 100 ways to do it so we just
found the uh the most Optimum way what
we found uh could be we could have done
and then use that but there are still
lot of open uh areas where we can look
into
it Habib shapu says plus one for Optimum
I had some issues setting up
dependencies but was simple from that
point on and also wants to know was any
comparison done on the quality of
results
quality of results for bite compared to
float 32 a short answer
no no um yeah so um we showed M showed
in beginning that triangle uh and then
circle around speed but of course if you
want to know everything you have to also
pay attention to the Quality aspect of
it you you're constantly making trades
off between cost speed and and quality
with Factor search especially and this
exercise zoomed and focus totally on a
speed aspect so we have enough enough
material hopefully next time for another
talk right and then we focus on
quality all right there no more
questions let's thank our
[Applause]
speakers
enjoy
e e